This is a bullet casing.
But I thought anything mechanical
was forbidden here, isn't it?
It means the underground rulers of the NGL
weren't only manufacturing drugs,
but weapons.
-Yeah, but judging by this…
-This wasn't a human.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
[narrator] The Chimera Ants continue
their rampage across the NGL
and have finally bared their fangs
at the underground ruler
who led this country from the shadows.
It's safe for us to assume that
the Chimera Ants have taken full control
of the NGL's interior.
I need much more than this!
I require more nutritious food
for this precious child.
If the queen commands it, we will gladly
double, or even triple our quota.
-Yes, but we must increase our ranks.
-Not so.
after we eliminate sedition
in every last one of--
-[Zazan] You've got to be joking!
-[all] Huh?
of a thousand of the normal ones.
We're calling them Rares
because they're quite difficult to find.
[Zazan] That's right.
Impossible. No such human could ever--
They do exist! Not only did I see one,
but I fought with it, too.
You're lying.
The one you took a bite out of
wasn't rare in the least.
Oh, yeah, you're right. I forgot.
Stop spouting nonsense.
I'm sorry, mistress,
but what you said was nonsense as well.
Well, I was the one who disabled him.
Maybe so.
But I was the one who caught him first.
[whimpers]
That story you told, so was it true?
[gasps] If it isn't, Lord Bihorn.
Of course, it really was a rare human.
No, not that.
Did you really take a bite out of it?
No. Well, I…
I just tasted the normal human,
not the rare one. [grunts]
I will never do it again.
Please, spare me just this once,
Lord Bihorn.
Hold it. Come back here at once!
-[Colt] Bihorn.
-[grunts]
I'm curious,
have you ever seen a rare human before?
Zazan, so this rare human,
can you tell me more about it?
Hmm, yes, that must be it.
Well, that does solve one mystery.
It seems the arrows in question,
while invisible to the foot soldiers,
can be seen by officers, like Pike.
That means we can stop them.
If so, that also means
we can capture them.
[Zazan] That's right, just like I did.
It was obvious, that one
was very different from the other humans
we've captured so far.
In fact, its entire body seemed to be
a shining mass of life energy,
and that's how I could tell
that Rares have the nutritional value
of over a thousand humans.
More than ten days' worth of sustenance
in one human?
[Turtle Ant] If that's true,
then we're all saved.
That will be significantly easier
than carrying a hundred or so humans
around with us every day.
Find one on the first day
and we can rest for the next nine.
Come on. They're rare because
they're so difficult to find, you idiot.
[Colt] What? Again?
-Yes, I understand.
-[Peggy] Is there something wrong?
It's about Rammot, it would seem that he's
chosen to act without my permission again.
[Rammot chomping]
I know why. It's because of Colt.
This is all his fault.
[Colt] I have to deal with Rammot first
before it sets a bad example.
[gasps]
This presence, what is it?
[footsteps approaching]
[Gon] Nobody's in here.
Hey, something smells bad.
It's coming from over there.
-What?
-What the hell is that thing?
[Kite] So, they can conceal
their presence.
[growls]
[shudders]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[growls]
[Kite] That's a Chimera Ant soldier.
There are bound to be plenty more like him
from here on out.
If you can't defeat him, go home.
-I've already told you Kite…
-We're both professionals, too.
[Rammot] What trick is this?
They seem to have gotten stronger
all of a sudden.
[Rammot yells]
[grunts, groans]
[Rammot screams]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[Gon] Show me rock!
Janken rock!
All right! A perfect shot!
[growls]
[roars]
I swear on my life,
you're both dead, you hear me?
[Gon] Our attacks didn't work.
[Kite] It's because that one's smart.
He just let his lackey in to fight,
so that we would tip our hand.
Are you coming?
Hey, don't be so disappointed.
Your attacks just now,
they weren't that bad.
You just need a bit more experience,
that's all.
If you wanna get stronger,
this is a perfect opportunity,
From here on out,
in victory or defeat, it'll be hell.
-Right, count us in.
-[Killua] Yeah.
[gagging]
[straining] God damn it!
It hurts! [groaning]
Don't you dare lay a finger on them.
[Rammot groaning]
I'm more than willing
to let you kill them,
but you may not eat them.
Bodies brimming with so much life energy
will make prime nourishment.
They must be fed to the queen,
you understand that?
Ugh! I can't just kill them
and walk away, I can't!
The other squads do it all the time,
they told me.
-Hold on, is that true?
-Yeah.
even if that means
I have to transfer to another unit.
[groaning] Damn it, it hurts!
That way, you get to know exactly
what they're thinking as they're dying.
I do enjoy seeing the fear on their faces.
It's the best!
Once you try it, you never go back.
It's true. [laughs]
You shouldn't be wasting the queen's
precious source of nutrition for sport.
[Leol chuckles] "Precious"?
Don't make me laugh.
Be honest, there are far more of them
than she would ever need.
They're nothing but trash.
See, all we're doing is taking out
the garbage. Got a problem with that?
[Hina] Of course, not. [giggles]
And did you know about the Rares
among the humans?
The Rares, huh?
Oh, you must be talking about the ones
that are overflowing with life energy.
I still haven't seen one yet myself.
If you ever do,
you must capture it alive
and bring it back here.
Hmm, whatever you say, boss.
I'll offer the rare ones to the queen.
Go tell that to Rammot,
maybe that'll get him to calm down.
[all laughing]
Opinions aren't necessarily a bad thing,
but too many of them are selfish.
[Cheetu] We're meeting our quota.
I don't see what there is to worry about.
[teases]
Tell me the truth, are you even counting
the humans you capture?
[Cheetu] Mmm, mostly.
That isn't helpful.
[Peggy] Perhaps we should have everyone
assembled to discuss this.
No, we all work different schedules
at the moment.
We cannot assemble everyone.
Let's talk to them individually
and see if we can come up with a plan.
Fine, but what about the queen?
That's right.
further intensifies the ominous air.
-[wind whistling]
-But what awaits Gon and his friends?
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] Next time, "Kite and Slots".
Start the slots. Brrr! Beep-beep-beep.
Click-click-click. Boom!
[singer singing in Japanese]